Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla TV Interviews
    - Shalom Gorewitz, 12/15/1981; 138.0050 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0050, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0050)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 62 min.
    - Marie Gould, NOVAC, 2/1/1984; 138.0051 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0051, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 38.0051)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 43 min.
    - John Giancola, New York, NYSCA, 6/11/1984; 138.0052 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0052, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0052)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 54 min.
    - Julie Gustafson, New York, discusses Global Village Documentaries. Part 1 of 2, 4/13/1984; 138.0053 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0053, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0053)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 90 min.
    - Julie Gustafson, New York, discusses Global Village Documentaries. Part 2 of 2, 4/13/1984; 138.0054 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0054, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0054)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 38 min.
    - DeeDee Halleck, 6/14//1986; 138.0055 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0055, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0055)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 82 min.
    - Barbara Haspiel, discusses NYSCA and video funding, 5/7/1984; 138.0056 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0056, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0056)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 94 min.
    - Mike Hazard, Minneapolis, University Community Video, 6/17/1983; 138.0057 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0057, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0057)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 73 min.
    - John Hellmore, Los Angeles, "Odd discussion, peripherally about Vermont Video Group and UCV", 10/13/1983; 138.0058 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0058, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0058)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 60 min.
    - Dorothy Hénault discussing George Stoney and Challenge for Change, 6/2000; 138.0059 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0059, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0059)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 48 min.
      Conditions Governing Access
      This title is currently unavailable.
    - Jamie Hindman and Larry Kirkman discussing AFI, 12/4/1981; 138.0060 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0060, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0060)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK Ad-C60, Duration: 50 min.
    - Perrin Ireland, Washington DC, discussing NEA support for video documentaries, 5/22/1984; 138.0061 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0061, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0061)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 46 min.
    - Jane Jensen, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC, 2/3/1984; 138.0062 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0062, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0062)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 00
    - Deanna Kamiel, Minneapolis, discusses Independent production staff at KCTA and women in television, 6/14/1983; 138.0063 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0063, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0063)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 89 min.
    - Judi Keleman, Boston, Women's Video Collective, 11/10/1983; 138.0064 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0064, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0064)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 46 min.
    - Joanne Kelly, San Francisco, discusses Video Free America and the problems of being a woman in video and documentary. Part 1 of 2, 10/7/1983; 138.0065 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0065, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0065)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 93 min.
    - Joanne Kelly, San Francisco, discusses Video Free America and the problems of being a woman in video and documentary. Part 2 of 2, 10/7/1983; 138.0066 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0066, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0066)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 43 min.
    - Howard Klein, New York, discusses Rockefeller Foundation and video funding., 3/20/1984; 138.0067 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0067, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0067)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Carole Anne Klonarides and Robin White, Soho TV. Part 2 of 2, 11/18/1981; 138.0068 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0068, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0068)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Lafayette Criterion 60, Duration: 95 min.
    - Luci Kostelanetz, discusses NYSCA, 5/2/1984; 138.0069 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0069, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0069)
    - Mitchell Kriegman, Part 1 of 2, 12/3/1981; 138.0070 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0070, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0070)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK Ad-C60, Duration: 63 min.
    - Mitchell Kriegman, Part 2 of 2, 12/3/1981; 138.0071 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0071, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0071)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 42 min.
    - Stephen Kulczycki, Los Angeles, discusses UCV and its collapse as a production house, 10/14/1983; 138.0072 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0072, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0072)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 85 min.
    - Ben Levine, discusses People's Video Theater and Woodstock Community Video. Part 1 of 2, 11/1/1984; 138.0073 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0073, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0073)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 89 min.
    - Ben Levine, discusses People's Video Theater and Woodstock Community Video. Part 2 of 2, 11/1/1984; 138.0074 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0074, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0074)
    - Wendy Lidell, AIVF, 12/3/1981; 138.0075 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0075, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0075)
    - Chip Lord, San Francisco, Ant Farm, 10/3/1985; 138.0076 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0076, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0076)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 69 min.
    - David Loxton, New York, discusses TV lab and TVTV among others, 4/2/1984; 138.0077 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0077, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0077)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 79 min.
    - Mary Lucier, 12/7/1981; 138.0078 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0078, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0078)
    - Mary Lucier, Part 1 of 2, 10/21/2001; 138.0079 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0079, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0079)
    - Mary Lucier, Part 2 of 2, 10/21/2001; 138.0080 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0080, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0080)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 28 min.
    - Curt Madison, 11/19/1984; 138.0081 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0081, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0081)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX60, Duration: 32 min.
    - Victor Masayevsa, Jr., discusses Native American Festival, 11/16/1984; 138.0082 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0082, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0082)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sanyo C-60, Duration: 63 min.
    - Ron McCoy, discusses the origins of University Community Video, 6/9/1983; 138.0083 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0083, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0083)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 87 min.
    - Susan Milano. Part 1 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0084 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0084, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0084)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX990, Duration: 94 min.
    - Susan Milano. Part 2 of 2, 5/15/1984; 138.0085 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0085, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0085)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 14 min.
    - Mary Milton and the Markle Foundation, October 12, 19zz, undated; 138.0086 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0086, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0086)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Certron LN60, Duration: 18 min.
    - Jim Morris, San Francisco, discusses producing "The Stag Hotel", 10/5/1983; 138.0087 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0087, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0087)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 79 min.
    - Jim Mulligan and Greg Pratt, Minneapolis, discuss UCV, its growth, development and the ongoing careers of both men, 6/14/1983; 138.0088 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0088, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0088)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 86 min.
    - Marty Newell, Whitesburg KY, discusses "Headwaters" a weekly video cable show, Part 1 of 2, 1/24/1984; 138.0089 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0089, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0089)
    - Marty Newell, Whitesburg KY, discusses "Headwaters" a weekly video cable show, Part 2 of 2, 1/24/1984; 138.0090 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0090, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0090)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 22 min.
    - Stevenson Palfi, Part 1 of 2, 8/9/1984; 138.0091 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0091, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0091)
    - Stevenson Palfi, Part 2 of 2, 8/9/1984; 138.0092 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0092, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0092)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 36 min.
    - Kath Quinn, New Orleans discusses NOVAC, the early years, 2/2/1984; 138.0093 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0093, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0093)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 47 min.
    - Karen Ranucci, New York, discusses DCTV, 6/13/1984; 138.0094 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0094, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0094)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 93 min.
    - John Reilly, New York, Global Village, Part 1 of 2, 4/17/1984; 138.0095 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0095, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0095)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90
    - John Reilly, New York, Global Village, Part 2 of 2, 4/17/1984; 138.0096 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0096, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0096)
    - Sherrie Rabinowitz, Santa Monica CA, discusses Optic Nerve and Rabinowitz-Galloway Satellite collaboration Part 1 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0097 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0097, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0097)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 87 min.
    - Sherrie Rabinowitz, Santa Monica CA, discusses Optic Nerve and Rabinowitz-Galloway satellite collaboration, Part 2 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0098 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0098, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0098)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 35 min.
    - Alan Rucker, TVTV. Part 1 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0099 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0099, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0099)
    - Alan Rucker, TVTV. Part 2 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0100 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0100, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0100)
    - Alan Rucker, discusses TVTV's 20 year reunion. Part 1 of 2, 3/8/1992; 138.0101 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0101, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0101)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 77 min.
    - Alan Rucker, discusses TVTV's 20 year reunion. Part 2 of 2, 3/8/1992; 138.0102 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0102, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0102)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, Duration: 19 min.
    - Paul Ryan, 10/29/1985; 138.0103 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0103, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0103)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90
    - Michael Shamberg, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV. Part 1 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0104 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0104, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0104)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 94 min.
    - Michael Shamberg, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV. Part 2 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0105 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0105, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0105)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 16 min.
    - Ira Schneider and Deena Krane. Part 1 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0106 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0106, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0106)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 63 min.
    - Ira Schneider and Deena Krane. Part 2 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0107 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0107, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0107)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 20 min.
    - Ira Schneider, 6/26/1984; 138.0108 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0108, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0108)
    - Kathy Seltzer, discusses Portable Channel, UCV and "The Fear the Binds Us", 6/16/1983; 138.0109 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0109, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0109)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 47 min.
    - John Shepherd and Barbara London, AFI, 6/1982; 138.0110 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0110, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0110)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 55 min.
    - Neil Sieling, Minneapolis, discusses UCV in transition, 6/17/1983; 138.0111 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0111, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0111)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, 39 min.
    - Lydia Sillman, New York, discusses NYSCA and video, programming for 77-78, 5/1/1984; 138.0112 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0112, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0112)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, 73 min.
    - Fred Simon, Boston, discusses pioneering video "Bobby the Fife," "New Wave," and "Frank: A Vietnam Vet", 11/9/1983; 138.0113 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0113, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0113)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 95 min.
    - Thea Sklover, New York, discusses Open Channel Public Access, 8/25/1983; 138.0114 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0114, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0114)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 81 min.
    - Ray Smith, Whitesburg KY, discusses the decline of Broadside TV, 1/25/1984; 138.0115 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0115, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0115)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 90 min.
    - Karen Snyder and Karen Kern, New Orleans, discuss NOVAC and "From the Stoop", 2/4/1984; 138.0116 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0116, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0116)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 69 min.
    - Elon Soltes, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV, the rift in the group toward the end, "Lord of the Universe" and April Video Collective. Part 1 of 2, 10/12/1983; 138.0117 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0117, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0117)
    - Elon Soltes, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV, the rift in the group toward the end, "Lord of the Universe" and April Video Collective. Part 2 of 2, 10/12/1983; 138.0118 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0118, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0118)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 44 min.
    - Phillip Stack, Sony executive. Part 1 of 2, 10/3/1984; 138.0119 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0119, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0119)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, OMNI Ultra Dynamic 90, 90 min.
    - Phillip Stack, Sony executive. Part 2 of 2, 10/3/1984; 138.0120 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0120, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0120)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, OMNI Ultra Dynamic 90, 8 min.
    - Adam Steg, New Orleans, discusses Synapse, NOVAC etc., 2/1/1984; 138.0121 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0121, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0121)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, 47 min.
    - Bill Stephens, discussing the People's Communication Network. Part 1 of 2, 5/10/1984; 138.0122 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0122, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0122)
      Original Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90
    - Bill Stephens, discusses the People's Communication Network. Part 2 of 2, 5/10/1984; 138.0123 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0123, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0123)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90
    - George Stoney Part 1 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0124 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0124, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0124)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 92 min.
    - George Stoney Part 2 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0125 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0125, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0125)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 37 min.
    - George Stoney Part 1 of 2, 6/27/2000; 138.0126 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0126, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0126)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 94 min.
    - George Stoney Part 2 of 2, 6/27/2000; 138.0127 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0127, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0127)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 18 min.
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America, 9/29/1983; 138.0128 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0128, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0128)
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America. Part 1 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0129 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0129, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0129)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell XLII90, 1 min.
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America and "My Father Sold Studebakers" Part 2 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0130 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0130, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0130)
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America. Part 3 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0131 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0131, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0131)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 61 min.
    - Parry Teasdale and Carol Vontobel, Phoenicia NY, discussing Videofreex and Lanesville TV. Part 1 of 2, 4/18/1984; 138.0132 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0132, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0132)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 93 min.
    - Parry Teasdale and Carol Vontobel, Phoenicia NY, discussing Videofreex and Lanesville TV. Part 2 of 2, 4/18/1984; 138.0133 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0133, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0133)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 94 min.
    - Rick Tejado-Flores, Los Angeles, 10/5/1983; 138.0134 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0134, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0134)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 67 min.
    - Mary Tiseo, Boston, discusses Urban Planning Aid, 11/11/1983; 138.0135 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0135, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0135)
    - TVTV "The Good Times Are Killing Me.", undated; 138.0136 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0136, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0136)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 60 min.
    - "TVTV at the Superbowl.", undated; 138.0137 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0137, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0137)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 39 min.
    - Eric Trigg and Howard Wise, EAI Video Art, 11/27/1981; 138.0138 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0138, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0138)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 58 min.
    - Arthur Tsuchiya, discusses Visual Studies Workshop (VSW), Ithaca Film and Video Art, 6/1981; 138.0139 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0139, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0139)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Realistic Supertape Cassette C-60, 66 min.
    - Keiko Tsuno, Part 1 of 2, 5/8/1984; 138.0140 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0140, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0140)
    - Keiko Tsuno, Part 2 of 2, 5/8/1984; 138.0141 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0141, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0141)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 34 min.
    - Edin Velez, New York, giving a lecture to Fordham students on his work. Part 1 of 2, 3/1983; 138.0142 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0142, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0142)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 63 min.
    - Edin Velez, New York, giving a lecture to Fordham students on his work. Part 2 of 2, 3/1983; 138.0143 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0143, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0143)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 54 min.
    - Bill Viola, Part 1 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0144 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0144, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0144)
    - Bill Viola, Part 2 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0145 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0145, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0145)
    - Bill Viola, Part 3 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0146 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0146, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0146)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 16 min.
    - Bill Viola, 11/1987; 138.0147 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0147, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0147)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Denon HD8-90, 94 min.
    - Ann Volkes, Part 1 of 2, 4/25/1984; 138.0148 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0148, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0148)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch C-90, 92 min.
    - Ann Volkes, Part 2 of 2, 4/25/1984; 138.0149 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0149, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0149)
    - Gail Waldron, Minneapolis, discusses BAVC and "The Life and Times of Rose Maddox", 6/11/1983; 138.0150 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0150, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0150)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 57 min.
    - Burwell Ware and Eddie Kurtz, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC. Part 1 of 2, 1/31/1984; 138.0151 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0151, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0151)
    - Burwell Ware and Eddie Kurtz, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC. Part 2 of 2, 1/31/1984; 138.0152 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0152, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0152)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 84 min.
    - Morrie Warshowski, San Francisco, discusses BAVC present and future, comments on Northwest video, 9/29/1983; 138.0153 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0153, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0153)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 47 min.
    - Don West, Part 1 of 2, 5/21/1984; 138.0154 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0154, E-records fales_mss138)
    - Don West, Part 2 of 2, 5/21/1984; 138.0155 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0155, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0155)
    - Megan Williams, Los Angeles, TVTV, 10/18/1983; 138.0156 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0156, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0156)
    - Ann Woodward, 4/10/1984; 138.0157 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0157, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0157)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 95 min.
  - Subseries B: Conferences
    - American Film Institute (AFI) "Role of the Subject" participants include Blumberg, Costello and Studs Terkel, June 11, 1982. Part 1 of 2, 138.0158 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0158, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0158)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 61 min.
    - AFI "Role of the Subject" participants include Blumberg, Costello and Studs Terkel, June 11, 1982. Part 2 of 2, 138.0159 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0159, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0159)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 5 min.
    - Association of Independent Video and Filmmakers (AIVF) "Docs to Drama" October 28, 1987. Part 1 of 2, 138.0160 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0160, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0160)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 94 min.
    - AIVF "Docs to Drama" October 28, 1987. Part 2 of 2, 138.0161 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0161, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0161)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 30 min.
    - American Library Association (ALA) "Video:An Alternative Information Service" June 1980. Part 1 of 2, 138.0162 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0162, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0162)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 63 min.
    - ALA "Video: An Alternative Information Service", June 1980. Part 2 of 2, 138.0163 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0163, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0163)